tigermobiles.com 2019-05-14

# Privacy Policy - TigerMobiles.com

TigerMobiles.com takes data protection of our customers very seriously.

Company info. In this Privacy Policy “we”, “us” and “our” means TigerMobiles.com. TigerMobiles.com complies with and is registered under the data protection laws in the United Kingdom and takes all reasonable care to prevent any unauthorised access to your personal data. You can [download our ICO data protection registration certificate here](https://www.tigermobiles.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/tiger-mobiles-data-protection-registation-certificate.pdf).

We respect the privacy of every individual who visits our site and have created this policy because we want you to feel confident about the privacy and security of your personal information. We maintain strict security protocol in the storage and disclosure of your information as required by law under the Data Protection Act 1998.

By using our website and mobile phone comparison services you are giving us permission to use your data as set out in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please refrain from using our website.

### How we will use your data

We may use your data to review and analyse market trends and to track sales data, including information on how you use our website, pages you have viewed and which website you used previously to visit ours. We may pass your data to third parties for analytical purposes.

All personal information you provide will be held in the strictest confidence and only used for the purpose of providing our service, subject to certain exclusions as described within this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions.

### Disclosure of information

We will endeavor to treat all your personal information as private and confidential. Other than under the terms of this Privacy Policy we will not disclose any of your information to any other parties unless:

  * We are legally compelled to do so
  * There is a duty to the public to disclose
  * Disclosure is required to protect our interest
  * Disclosure is made at your request or with your consent
  * Information about our services
  * TigerMobiles.com may use the information you supply to contact you by phone, email, SMS or otherwise about products and services which may be of interest to you. Such services could include our newsletter and exclusive offers.

If you are not happy for your data to be used in this way, you can unsubscribe in a number of ways, including:

  * Click on the ‘unsubscribe’ link provided on each email we send to you
  * Email feedback@tigermobiles.com or
  * Use the ‘Contact Us’ form on the TigerMobiles.com website.
  * Please remember that by opting out, we will not be able to contact you about products or services that may benefit you.

### Contract Phones

Many mobile phone retailers and network providers operate a credit scoring system that will checked with credit reference agencies, fraud prevention agencies and other public or privately available sources of information. These checks will include electoral roll and credit information.

Applications you submit for a phone contract may affect your credit score so you may wish to keep applications to a minimum to protect your credit rating.

These credit checks are not being carried out because you are using TigerMobiles.com, nor are they conducted by TigerMobiles.com, but may be processed by any provider at any stage of a quote or purchase process.

### Unsolicited marketing policy

If you click through to any third party website, we cannot guarantee you will not be contacted by them. We would recommend that you read their Terms and Conditions and their Privacy Policy concerning your right to opt-out from contact by them.

### Help with choosing a contract phone

Many of our customers have told us that they appreciate extra information about choosing the right contract phone from the provider. For this reason by agreeing to the conditions laid out in this Privacy Policy you agree that your details may be used by “us”, the mobile phone / network provider or, where they are involved, their appointed representatives, or an intermediary to contact you with a view to seeing if you are interested in purchase, highlighting any special offers or ways they might be able to help you get an even cheaper price on a mobile phone contract.

### Your rights to your personal data

If you want to know what personal information we hold about you, we will provide you with this data. If any information held is inaccurate, we will make the necessary amendments and confirm to you that these have been made. If you wish to make a request under the terms of the Data Protection Act 1998 (DPA), for the personal information we hold about you, please write to us at:

### Data Protection Officer

 **Tiger Mobiles Limited**

15 Queen Square  
Leeds  
West Yorkshire  
LS2 8AJ  
United Kingdom

Please enclose two forms of identification displaying your name, address and/or date of birth (please send photocopies) and a cheque for the statutory administration fee of £10.00 made payable to TigerMobiles.com. We are entitled to charge you this fee under the DPA to cover our administration costs.

If you have any enquiry about our data protection and privacy policy or practices, please write to the Data Protection Officer at the above address.

### Removal of personal information

If you would like us to remove any personal information from our records, then please write to our Data Protection Officer at TigerMobiles.com, feedback@tigermobiles.com. We will make all reasonable efforts to delete your information from our files if it is deemed appropriate.

### Monitoring

Monitoring or recording of your calls, emails, text messages and other communications may take place in accordance with UK law, and in particular for business purposes such as: quality control and training; processing necessary for the entering into or the performance of a contract; to prevent unauthorised use of our telecommunications systems and web sites and/or services; to ensure effective systems operation; to meet any legal obligation; in your vital interests; in order to prevent or detect crime; and for the purposes of the legitimate interests of the data controller. Please visit the following websites for further information:

www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk  
www.berr.gov.uk

### Cookies

At TigerMobiles.com we respect your privacy and therefore we will only use ‘cookies’ where your browser enables us to do so. A cookie is a tiny piece of code, like a tag, which websites can place on your computer when you visit them, and act as a unique identifier that can be used to retrieve your records from databases, and to track your movement within the website.

We use ‘cookies’ to help you navigate through our site and to improve security. To find out more about cookies used by us, please read our Cookie Policy.

### Law

These terms of trading are subject to English law and to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English courts. You acknowledge that by providing data to us, you consent to the processing of your data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We reserve the right to amend or modify our Privacy Policy at any time and in response to changes in applicable data protection and privacy legislation.

Dated: 20/05/14
